Okay, so now we are going to go ahead and start filling our basket.
Now, we want it to look full but we don't want it to look cluttered.
So it is important that you pick some things, that when, whatever you pick out that you kind of take a couple minutes to find the right spot for them.
It might take a few minutes.
You may have to play around with it but that?s part of the fun.
Also, in terms of what you use, what you use in the basket to fill it, a good idea is going down to your local discount store or your Dollar Store and just going through the bins and just finding lots of little trinkets.
There is lots of things.
Lots of options and choices out there that little girls love.
And also in the children's section, the toy section.
But you don't have to spend a lot of money on expensive toys.
Because, after all, I think, I think it really a basket like this is more of a quantity.
You can never have too many headbands.
So I picked up a couple and I am going to go ahead and just, I think, stick them back here.
And everything doesn't have to be out in the open.
You can make them go digging for stuff.
That is also part of the fun.
You can certainly hide things under the grass.
But I think that this is a nice beginning of a display.
And again, play around with it however you like.
And now we are going to go and fill it in with a few more little trinkets.